smartersubmit.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

# To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

# To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**What is our Opt-out Policy for Subscribers?**

Once you subscribe we will send you special offers, deals and tips. You may opt-out and unsubscribe at any time. To opt-out you will see an Unsubscribe Me link at the end of every email you receive. Simply click that link and confirm that you want to opt-out and you will stop receiving mails from us. 

**Refund Policy**

Unfortunately due to the nature of work our services are non-refundable, all sales are full and final. Due to spikes and workload some projects may be delayed from time to time, for this you will receive an updates from our project manager.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

**Smarter Internet Marketing Private Limited**  
No. A 53, 1st Floor, Electronic Sadan No.1,   
Near Mahape Bus Depot, Mahape,  
Navi Mumbai , Maharashtra   
400710   
India
